export const GameData = [
  {
    id: 'c1',
    isLocked: false,
    story:
      "'Welcome! I'm James Bartlett, your guide on this captivating journey through the Chronicles of Time.The city of Christchurch, renowned for its rich historical heritage, invites you to dive into an exciting story that began in the mid-19th century. Throughout this journey, you will learn about the fascinating moments of Christchurch's founding, its early settlements, development, and emergence as one of New Zealand's most significant cities. From ancient buildings to key historical events – you will discover everything that has made this city so special. Don't miss the chance to explore more about Christchurch's intriguing path!'",
    level: 1,
    name: 'Chronicles of Time',
    easy: [
      {
        question:
          'Which European nation was the first to explore the area where Christchurch is now located?',
        options: ['French', 'Spanish', 'British', 'Dutch'],
        correctAnswer: 'British',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who was the first European to land on the shores of what would become Christchurch?',
        options: [
          'James Cook',
          'Abel Tasman',
          'Jean-François de La Pérouse',
          'Samuel Marsden',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'James Cook',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the famous garden located in the center of Christchurch that is part of the city's historical heritage?",
        options: [
          'Christchurch Botanic Gardens',
          'Garden of Blooming Dreams',
          'Royal Garden',
          'Maori Garden',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Christchurch Botanic Gardens',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What significant natural feature is located near Christchurch and is frequently visited by tourists?',
        options: [
          'Lake Tekapo',
          'Franz Josef Glacier',
          'Mount Cook',
          'Banks Peninsula',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Banks Peninsula',
      },
      {
        question: 'What animal is a symbol of the city of Christchurch?',
        options: ['Kiwi', 'Kaka', 'Kereru', 'Royal Albatross'],
        correctAnswer: 'Kiwi',
      },
      {
        question: 'In what year did Christchurch gain city status?',
        options: ['1856', '1860', '1868', '1871'],
        correctAnswer: '1856',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which architect designed the famous Christchurch Cathedral?',
        options: [
          'George Gilbert Scott',
          'Francis Petre',
          'Benjamin Montfort',
          'John Loughborough Pearson',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Benjamin Montfort',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which historical event significantly affected the architecture of Christchurch in 2011?',
        options: ['Tsunami', 'Earthquake', 'Great Fire', 'Flood'],
        correctAnswer: 'Earthquake',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What old-fashioned mode of transport is still used in Christchurch for tourists?',
        options: [
          'Steam locomotive',
          'Paddle steamer',
          'Tram',
          'Hot air balloon',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Tram',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which museum in Christchurch houses a collection of ancient Maori artifacts?',
        options: [
          'Canterbury Museum',
          'Otago Museum',
          'Tapu Tapu Museum',
          'National Museum of New Zealand',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Canterbury Museum',
      },
    ],
    hard: [
      {
        question:
          'Was Great Britain the first European nation to explore the area where Christchurch is now located?',
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Was James Cook the first European to land on the shores of what would become Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Christchurch Botanic Gardens a famous garden located in the center of the city that is part of its historical heritage?',
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Banks Peninsula a significant natural feature near Christchurch that is frequently visited by tourists?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question: 'Is the kiwi the symbol of the city of Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question: 'Did Christchurch gain city status in 1860?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Was the famous Christchurch Cathedral designed by George Gilbert Scott?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Did the 2011 earthquake significantly affect the architecture of Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is a paddle steamer still used as a tourist transport in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Are ancient Maori artifacts housed in the Otago Museum in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
    ],
    coordinates: {
      latitude: -43.538,
      longitude: 172.635,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 'c2',
    isLocked: false,
    story:
      "Greetings! I'm James Bartlett, your guide along the River Avon, Christchurch's true lifeblood. The River Avon, which flows through the center of our city, is of great historical and cultural importance to Christchurch. Its waters not only provide beauty and tranquility, but also play a key role in the development of the city. By following its course, we can feel a connection to the historical past and the cultural changes that have taken place in Christchurch over the centuries. The river was an important resource for early settlers, and today it remains a favorite place for recreation and entertainment. Exploring the Avon River opens up a fascinating journey into the city's past and present. Don't miss the opportunity to learn more about this important part of our city!",
    level: 2,
    name: 'River Avon: The lifeblood of the city',
    easy: [
      {
        question:
          'What cultural significance does the Avon River hold for Christchurch?',
        options: [
          'It is the site of annual sports competitions',
          'It is a popular fishing spot for locals',
          'It symbolizes the connection between the city and nature',
          'It is used as a source of hydroelectric power',
        ],
        correctAnswer:
          'It symbolizes the connection between the city and nature',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What well-known activity on the Avon River attracts tourists to Christchurch?',
        options: ['Fishing', 'Punting on boats', 'Scuba diving', 'Skiing'],
        correctAnswer: 'Punting on boats',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What role does the Avon River play in Christchurch's economy?",
        options: [
          'It is the source of fresh water for the city',
          'It contributes to tourism development',
          'It is a site for mineral extraction',
          'It is used for transporting goods',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'It contributes to tourism development',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What type of landscape surrounds the Avon River in Christchurch?',
        options: [
          'Dense tropical forests',
          'High mountains',
          'Urban parks and gardens',
          'Sandy deserts',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Urban parks and gardens',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which historical event is associated with the Avon River in Christchurch?',
        options: [
          'The founding of the first settlement in the city',
          'A battle between settlers and the Māori',
          'The discovery of a gold deposit',
          "A major flood that changed the river's course",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The founding of the first settlement in the city',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which animals are typical representatives of the fauna of the Avon River?',
        options: [
          'Penguins',
          'Ducks and swans',
          'Kiwis and tuataras',
          'Sea lions',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ducks and swans',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which plants are most commonly found along the Avon River?',
        options: [
          'Flowering meadows and tree ferns',
          'Cacti and succulents',
          'Vineyards',
          'Tall palm trees',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Flowering meadows and tree ferns',
      },
      {
        question: 'Why was the Avon River named so?',
        options: [
          'It was named after a mythical creature',
          'It was named after a river in Scotland',
          'The name was given by the Māori',
          'It was named for its clear color',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'It was named after a river in Scotland',
      },
      {
        question:
          "How does the Avon River impact Christchurch's environmental state?",
        options: [
          'It is a source of pollution',
          'It provides the city with a natural environment and promotes biodiversity',
          'It is a site for industrial waste storage',
          'It causes regular floods',
        ],
        correctAnswer:
          'It provides the city with a natural environment and promotes biodiversity',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What role does the Avon River play in the modern life of Christchurch residents?',
        options: [
          'Exclusively an aesthetic role',
          'The main source of drinking water',
          'A place for recreation and cultural events',
          'Used for transportation purposes',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'A place for recreation and cultural events',
      },
    ],
    hard: [
      {
        question:
          'Is the Avon River an important tourist attraction in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question: 'Is the Avon River surrounded by dense tropical forests?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Avon River the site of annual punting (boating) competitions?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Does the Avon River have a significant impact on the city's economy through tourism development?",
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question: 'Was the Avon River named after a river in Scotland?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Avon River associated with the founding of the first settlement in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question: 'Is the Avon River a source of pollution in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Are ducks and swans typical representatives of the fauna of the Avon River?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Avon River used as the main source of drinking water for the city?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Avon River a place for recreation and cultural events in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
    ],
    coordinates: {
      latitude: -43.5367,
      longitude: 172.648,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 'c3',
    isLocked: false,
    story:
      "Congratulations! I'm James Bartlett, your guide to the fascinating world of art and literature in Christchurch. Christchurch has a long and varied history in art and literature, stretching from classical times to modern times. Our city has become a center for numerous artists, writers and cultural figures who have invested their creativity in the development of our cultural environment. From early literary works inspired by the beauty of natural landscapes to contemporary artistic movements, Christchurch offers a rich spectrum of cultural influences and achievements. Here you will find numerous galleries, theaters and literary events that demonstrate the evolution of art and literature over the years. Get ready to immerse yourself in the world of creativity that has become an important part of Christchurch life.",
    level: 3,
    name: 'Christchurch Art and Literature: From the Classics to the Contemporary',
    easy: [
      {
        question:
          'Which famous Christchurch-born writer won the Nobel Prize in Literature in 2000?',
        options: [
          'Margaret Mahy',
          'Keri Hulme',
          'Janet Frame',
          'Eleanor Catton',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Keri Hulme',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the iconic art gallery located in Christchurch that showcases both classical and contemporary art?',
        options: [
          'Christchurch Art Museum',
          'Canterbury Art Space',
          'Christchurch Art Gallery Te Puna o Waiwhetū',
          'Southern Arts Centre',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Christchurch Art Gallery Te Puna o Waiwhetū',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which literary genre is Christchurch author Margaret Mahy best known for?',
        options: [
          'Science fiction',
          "Children's literature",
          'Mystery novels',
          'Historical fiction',
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Children's literature",
      },
      {
        question:
          'What annual festival in Christchurch celebrates local and international writers, bringing together authors, poets, and readers?',
        options: [
          'Christchurch Literary Festival',
          'Word Christchurch',
          'Canterbury Book Fair',
          "Avon Writers' Gathering",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Word Christchurch',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which 19th-century artist is known for their landscape paintings depicting the Canterbury Plains and surrounding areas?',
        options: [
          'Charles Goldie',
          'Frances Hodgkins',
          'John Gibb',
          'Petrus Van der Velden',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'John Gibb',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which contemporary Christchurch poet is known for their work exploring themes of identity and belonging in New Zealand?',
        options: [
          'Selina Tusitala Marsh',
          'Tusiata Avia',
          'Bill Maher',
          'Michele Leggott',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Tusiata Avia',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What significant event in Christchurch's history has inspired many works of art and literature, reflecting the resilience of the city's people?",
        options: [
          'The 2011 earthquake',
          'The founding of the city',
          'The Great Depression',
          'The Canterbury Floods',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The 2011 earthquake',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which art form has become increasingly popular in Christchurch, particularly in the wake of the 2011 earthquake, as a means of urban regeneration?',
        options: [
          'Sculpture',
          'Street art',
          'Traditional painting',
          'Digital art',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Street art',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Christchurch author wrote the internationally acclaimed novel The Luminaries, which won the Man Booker Prize in 2013?',
        options: [
          'Janet Frame',
          'Keri Hulme',
          'Eleanor Catton',
          'Patricia Grace',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Eleanor Catton',
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which Christchurch-based theater company is known for its innovative productions and contributions to New Zealand's performing arts scene?",
        options: [
          'The Court Theatre',
          'Christchurch Repertory Theatre',
          'Avon Players',
          'Southern Stage Company',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Court Theatre',
      },
    ],
    hard: [
      {
        question:
          'Did Keri Hulme, a Christchurch-born writer, win the Nobel Prize in Literature?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Christchurch Art Gallery Te Puna o Waiwhetū known for showcasing both classical and contemporary art?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Is Margaret Mahy best known for her contributions to New Zealand's science fiction literature?",
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Word Christchurch an annual festival that celebrates local and international writers?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Did John Gibb, a 19th-century artist, focus primarily on portraits rather than landscapes?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Tusiata Avia a contemporary Christchurch poet known for exploring themes of identity and belonging?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Did the 2011 earthquake in Christchurch inspire many works of art and literature?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Has street art become an increasingly popular art form in Christchurch, especially after the 2011 earthquake?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Did Eleanor Catton's novel The Luminaries win the Man Booker Prize in 2013?",
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is The Court Theatre in Christchurch known for its traditional and conservative productions?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
    ],
    coordinates: {
      latitude: -43.538,
      longitude: 172.627,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 'c4',
    isLocked: true,
    story:
      "Congratulations! I'm James Bartlett, your guide to the world of Christchurch tech. Christchurch is a city that has always been at the forefront of technological progress. From the first industrial revolutions to modern startups and environmental initiatives, our city is celebrated as a place of innovation and change. Technologies that were once a novelty have now become part of our daily lives. As you explore Christchurch's history, you'll see how technological advances have shaped the city's development and how innovation continues to shape our future. Get ready to learn about the fascinating technological periods that have made Christchurch what it is today.",
    level: 4,
    name: 'Technological development: From the past to the present',
    easy: [
      {
        question:
          'Which industry was one of the first to develop in Christchurch during the Industrial Revolution?',
        options: [
          'Textile industry',
          'Timber industry',
          'Dairy industry',
          'Steel production',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Dairy industry',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which scientific center in Christchurch is a leader in research and technology development?',
        options: [
          'Christchurch Science Hub',
          'Canterbury Innovation Centre',
          'Tait Technology Centre',
          'Southern Research Institute',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Tait Technology Centre',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which technology company founded in Christchurch became famous for its innovations in wireless communications?',
        options: ['Tait Communications', 'Fisher & Paykel', 'Xero', 'Navman'],
        correctAnswer: 'Tait Communications',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which environmental project in Christchurch exemplifies sustainable development and the use of renewable energy sources?',
        options: [
          'Zero Waste Christchurch',
          'Christchurch Solar City',
          'Sustainable Christchurch Initiative',
          'EcoCentral Christchurch',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'EcoCentral Christchurch',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What role does Christchurch play in the development of New Zealand's space industry?",
        options: [
          'Christchurch is a center for satellite production',
          'Christchurch hosts one of the largest spaceports',
          'Christchurch is an important center for space technology development and research',
          'Christchurch is the main city for rocket launches',
        ],
        correctAnswer:
          'Christchurch is an important center for space technology development and research',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which initiative in Christchurch supports startups and technological innovation?',
        options: [
          'Canterbury Startup Network',
          'Christchurch Innovation Incubator',
          'GreenTech Christchurch',
          'Ministry of Awesome',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ministry of Awesome',
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which historical factory in Christchurch became a symbol of the city's industrial development?",
        options: [
          'Woolston Foundry',
          'Christchurch Woollen Mills',
          'Canterbury Ironworks',
          'Avon Cotton Factory',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Christchurch Woollen Mills',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which scientific institution in Christchurch specializes in agritech and agricultural research?',
        options: [
          'Lincoln University',
          'University of Canterbury',
          'Christchurch Polytechnic Institute of Technology',
          'Canterbury Agricultural Research Centre',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Lincoln University',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What innovative solution in Christchurch is used to reduce the environmental impact of cars?',
        options: [
          'Introduction of electric vehicles',
          'Development of bike lanes',
          'Construction of high-speed electric trains',
          'Launch of a car-sharing program',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Launch of a car-sharing program',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which technology is actively used in Christchurch to monitor natural disasters such as earthquakes?',
        options: [
          'Early tsunami warning systems',
          'Drones for aerial photography',
          'Geoseismic sensors',
          'Satellite systems',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Geoseismic sensors',
      },
    ],
    hard: [
      {
        question:
          'Was the dairy industry one of the first sectors to develop in Christchurch during the Industrial Revolution?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Tait Technology Centre a leading scientific center in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Tait Communications a well-known Christchurch company working in the field of wireless communications?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is EcoCentral Christchurch an example of sustainable development in the city?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Does Christchurch play a key role in the production of satellites for New Zealand's space industry?",
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Does the Ministry of Awesome initiative support startups and technological innovation in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Christchurch Woollen Mills a historic factory that symbolizes the industrial development of Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Does Lincoln University specialize in agritech and agricultural research?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is car-sharing an innovative solution in Christchurch to reduce the environmental impact of cars?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Are geoseismic sensors used in Christchurch to monitor earthquakes?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
    ],
    coordinates: {
      latitude: -43.53,
      longitude: 172.644,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 'c5',
    isLocked: true,
    story:
      "I congratulate you! James Bartlett, your guide to the world of Christchurch's green spaces. Christchurch is not only a city with a rich history and culture, but also an oasis of greenery. Our parks and gardens, such as Hagley Park and Christchurch Botanic Gardens, are the heart of the city and important parts of its heritage. These green spaces not only give us beauty and peace, but are also places for recreation, cultural events and social gatherings. Each park and garden has its own history and significance, which you can explore to better understand how they have influenced the life of the city and its residents. I invite you to explore these wonderful green spaces in Christchurch and learn more about their role in our cultural and natural heritage.",
    level: 5,
    name: "Green Christchurch: The city's parks and gardens",
    easy: [
      {
        question:
          'Which large park in Christchurch is known for its expansive green spaces and is a central location for many city events?',
        options: [
          'Victoria Park',
          'Hagley Park',
          'Botanic Gardens',
          'Mona Vale',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Hagley Park',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the famous botanical garden located in the center of Christchurch, renowned for its diverse plant collections?',
        options: [
          'Christchurch Botanic Gardens',
          'Garden of Eden',
          'Canterbury Gardens',
          'Rose Park',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Christchurch Botanic Gardens',
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which Christchurch park features a large, historic greenhouse known as the 'Cranesbill House'?",
        options: [
          'Hagley Park',
          'Botanic Gardens',
          'Sumner Park',
          'Riccarton Bush',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Botanic Gardens',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Christchurch garden is celebrated for its extensive collection of native New Zealand plants?',
        options: [
          'Hagley Park',
          'Christchurch Botanic Gardens',
          'The Garden of Native Plants',
          'Riccarton House Gardens',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Garden of Native Plants',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What significant event in 2011 had a major impact on the parks and gardens in Christchurch?',
        options: [
          'The Christchurch City Council decision to close several parks',
          'The opening of new green spaces',
          'The Christchurch earthquake',
          'The creation of new urban parks',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Christchurch earthquake',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which park in Christchurch is known for its historical significance and features a large pond and numerous walking paths?',
        options: [
          'Victoria Park',
          'Hagley Park',
          'Botanic Gardens',
          'New Brighton Park',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Victoria Park',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the primary purpose of the Christchurch Botanic Gardens?',
        options: [
          'To provide a venue for outdoor sports',
          'To serve as a community center',
          'To display and preserve a wide variety of plant species',
          'To offer amusement park rides',
        ],
        correctAnswer:
          'To display and preserve a wide variety of plant species',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Christchurch park is located near the University of Canterbury and is a popular spot for students and families?',
        options: [
          'Mona Vale',
          'Hagley Park',
          'Riccarton Bush',
          'Victoria Park',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Riccarton Bush',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What type of wildlife can commonly be spotted in the Christchurch Botanic Gardens?',
        options: [
          'Penguins and seals',
          'Ducks and swans',
          'Koalas and kangaroos',
          'Eagles and hawks',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ducks and swans',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Christchurch garden is known for its beautiful rose displays and is a popular location for weddings?',
        options: [
          'The Rose Garden at Hagley Park',
          'Botanic Gardens',
          'Victoria Park',
          'The Garden of Roses',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Rose Garden at Hagley Park',
      },
    ],
    hard: [
      {
        question:
          'Is Hagley Park known for its large green spaces and is a central location for many city events?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Christchurch Botanic Gardens renowned for its extensive collection of plant species?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Does the Christchurch Botanic Gardens feature a historic greenhouse known as the 'Cranesbill House'?",
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is The Garden of Native Plants celebrated for its collection of native New Zealand flora?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Did the Christchurch earthquake in 2011 have a major impact on the city's parks and gardens?",
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Victoria Park known for its large pond and numerous walking paths?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Does the primary purpose of the Christchurch Botanic Gardens include displaying and preserving a wide variety of plant species?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Riccarton Bush a park located near the University of Canterbury and popular with students and families?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Can ducks and swans commonly be spotted in the Christchurch Botanic Gardens?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the Rose Garden at Hagley Park known for its beautiful rose displays and popular for weddings?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
    ],
    coordinates: {
      latitude: -43.533,
      longitude: 172.629,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 'c6',
    isLocked: true,
    story:
      "Congratulations! I'm James Bartlett, your guide to the world of Christchurch Gothic architecture. Christchurch is a city where Victorian Gothic architecture has left its mark. Since the end of the 19th century, our streets have been decorated with majestic Gothic buildings reflecting the architectural style of that era. Christchurch's Gothic buildings, such as Christchurch Cathedral and other iconic structures, are examples of architectural art that combines elegance and strength. These architectural masterpieces not only decorate the city, but also tell about its history and development. Prepare to travel back in time to explore how Gothic architecture shaped the city and left a legacy that still fascinates and amazes today.",
    level: 6,
    name: "Christchurch's Gothic Architecture: A Victorian Legacy",
    easy: [
      {
        question:
          'Which famous Christchurch building is an example of Gothic Revival architecture from the Victorian era?',
        options: [
          'The Christchurch Town Hall',
          'The Canterbury Museum',
          'The Christchurch Cathedral',
          'The Arts Centre',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Christchurch Cathedral',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What style of architecture was predominant in Christchurch during the late 19th century?',
        options: ['Art Deco', 'Modernist', 'Gothic Revival', 'Baroque'],
        correctAnswer: 'Gothic Revival',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which architect is known for designing several Gothic Revival buildings in Christchurch, including the Christchurch Cathedral?',
        options: [
          'George Gilbert Scott',
          'Benjamin Montfort',
          'Francis Petre',
          'William Armstrong',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Benjamin Montfort',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What feature is commonly associated with Gothic Revival architecture that can be seen in Christchurch's historic buildings?",
        options: [
          'Flat roofs',
          'Ornate stone carvings and spires',
          'Large plate glass windows',
          'Minimalist design',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ornate stone carvings and spires',
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which Christchurch building served as the city's main public library and is an example of Victorian Gothic architecture?",
        options: [
          'The Christchurch Public Library',
          'The Canterbury Museum',
          'The Arts Centre',
          'The Christchurch Town Hall',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Christchurch Public Library',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the Christchurch building that was originally constructed as a college and features elements of Gothic Revival architecture?',
        options: [
          "The Christchurch Boys' High School",
          'The University of Canterbury',
          "The Christchurch Girls' High School",
          'The Arts Centre',
        ],
        correctAnswer: "The Christchurch Girls' High School",
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Christchurch landmark was heavily damaged in the 2011 earthquake but remains a prominent example of Victorian Gothic design?',
        options: [
          'The Arts Centre',
          'The Christchurch Cathedral',
          'The Canterbury Museum',
          "The Christ's College",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Christchurch Cathedral',
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which material is commonly used in Victorian Gothic architecture and is prevalent in Christchurch's Gothic Revival buildings?",
        options: ['Concrete', 'Brick and stone', 'Glass', 'Steel'],
        correctAnswer: 'Brick and stone',
      },
      {
        question:
          'The Gothic Revival style in Christchurch architecture was influenced by which earlier European architectural tradition?',
        options: [
          'Classical Greek',
          'Romanesque',
          'Gothic architecture from the Middle Ages',
          'Renaissance',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Gothic architecture from the Middle Ages',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following features is typically found in Victorian Gothic churches in Christchurch?',
        options: [
          'Large dome',
          'Stained glass windows',
          'Flat, expansive interiors',
          'Modernist abstract art',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Stained glass windows',
      },
    ],
    hard: [
      {
        question:
          'Is the Christchurch Cathedral an example of Gothic Revival architecture from the Victorian era?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Was the Gothic Revival style predominant in Christchurch architecture during the early 20th century?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Benjamin Mountfort known for designing Gothic Revival buildings in Christchurch, including the Christchurch Cathedral?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Are ornate stone carvings and spires commonly associated with Gothic Revival architecture in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Was the Christchurch Public Library originally constructed in Victorian Gothic style?',
        correctAnswer: false,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Does the Christchurch Girls' High School feature elements of Gothic Revival architecture?",
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Was the Christchurch Cathedral heavily damaged in the 2011 earthquake?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is brick and stone a commonly used material in Victorian Gothic architecture in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Was the Gothic Revival style in Christchurch influenced by medieval Gothic architecture from Europe?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Are stained glass windows a typical feature of Victorian Gothic churches in Christchurch?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
    ],
    coordinates: {
      latitude: -43.536,
      longitude: 172.643,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 'c7',
    isLocked: true,
    story:
      "Congratulations! James Bartlett, your guide to Christchurch's world of cultural diversity. Christchurch is a true cultural mosaic, where each nationality and ethnic group has made its unique contribution to the development of the city. Our city is marked by a wealth of cultural traditions, reflected in annual festivals, cuisine, art and social life. From Maori traditions to European, Asian and other cultures, Christchurch is a place where different cultural heritages intersect and enrich each other. Christchurch's multiculturalism creates a lively and dynamic atmosphere that makes our city so special. I invite you to explore these fascinating cultural aspects and learn how they shape our city.",
    level: 7,
    name: "Christchurch's Cultural Mosaic: A Multicultural City",
    easy: [
      {
        question:
          'Which festival in Christchurch celebrates Māori culture and traditions with performances, food, and art?',
        options: [
          'The Christchurch Festival of Lights',
          'The Māori Arts Festival',
          'The Christchurch Lantern Festival',
          'The Ngāi Tahu Festival',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Ngāi Tahu Festival',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which cultural group has a significant influence on the culinary scene in Christchurch, with numerous restaurants offering traditional dishes?',
        options: ['European', 'Māori', 'Asian', 'African'],
        correctAnswer: 'Asian',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the cultural precinct in Christchurch that highlights the contributions of various ethnic communities through art and exhibitions?',
        options: [
          'The Arts Centre',
          'The Cultural Hub',
          'The Christchurch Museum',
          'The Te Puna O Waiwhetū (Christchurch Art Gallery)',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Te Puna O Waiwhetū (Christchurch Art Gallery)',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which local Christchurch organization focuses on promoting the cultural heritage and traditions of the Pacific Islander community?',
        options: [
          'The Pacific Island Cultural Association',
          'The Māori Cultural Trust',
          'The Christchurch Pacific Island Community Group',
          'The Polynesian Arts Society',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Christchurch Pacific Island Community Group',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What type of traditional Māori performances can be seen during Christchurch's cultural events?",
        options: ['Ballet', 'Opera', 'Haka and waiata', 'Jazz'],
        correctAnswer: 'Haka and waiata',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Christchurch neighborhood is known for its vibrant Asian community and cultural festivals?',
        options: ['Riccarton', 'Sumner', 'Merivale', 'Linwood'],
        correctAnswer: 'Riccarton',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is a popular cultural event in Christchurch that showcases the diverse music and dance traditions of different cultures?',
        options: [
          'The Christchurch Music Festival',
          'The International Cultural Festival',
          'The Kiwi Arts Extravaganza',
          'The Multicultural Music Parade',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The International Cultural Festival',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Christchurch museum offers exhibits related to the history and culture of various immigrant communities in New Zealand?',
        options: [
          'Canterbury Museum',
          'Christchurch Art Gallery',
          'The National History Museum',
          'The New Zealand Heritage Centre',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Canterbury Museum',
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which European cultural influence can be seen in Christchurch's architectural style and local festivals?",
        options: ['Scandinavian', 'Italian', 'British', 'French'],
        correctAnswer: 'British',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the primary focus of the Christchurch-based cultural events that celebrate the contributions of different ethnic groups to the city's development?",
        options: [
          'Food and cuisine',
          'Traditional dances',
          'Art and cultural exhibitions',
          'Sports',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Art and cultural exhibitions',
      },
    ],
    hard: [
      {
        question:
          'Does the Ngāi Tahu Festival in Christchurch celebrate Māori culture and traditions?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Is the Asian culinary influence prominent in Christchurch's food scene?",
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Does the Te Puna O Waiwhetū (Christchurch Art Gallery) showcase art and exhibitions related to various ethnic communities?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Does the Christchurch Pacific Island Community Group focus on promoting Pacific Islander cultural heritage?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Can you see traditional Māori performances, such as haka and waiata, at Christchurch cultural events?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is Riccarton known for its vibrant Asian community and cultural festivals?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Is the International Cultural Festival a popular event in Christchurch that showcases diverse music and dance traditions?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Does the Canterbury Museum offer exhibits related to the history and culture of various immigrant communities in New Zealand?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Is British cultural influence evident in Christchurch's architectural style and local festivals?",
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Do Christchurch-based cultural events primarily focus on art and cultural exhibitions celebrating different ethnic groups?',
        correctAnswer: true,
      },
    ],
    coordinates: {
      latitude: -43.533,
      longitude: 172.636,
    },
  },
];
